You were in Osaka the other day for a staplerocalism session with Ijinari Tohokun and Batty Schultei.
How was it? How was that event?
We each played a cover song.
And Shachi was Tohokusan's Azatho.
Azatho on purpose.
What? I forgot already.
We just did it the other day.
On purpose, on purpose.
I can't do it anymore.
Expert in bruises, on purpose.
Yes, you are correct.
I was allowed to cover the song,
Basho had me cover a song called "Festivities," and Shachi had me cover
You have one of the prettiest parts, don't you?
Yes, that's right.
May I ask you to do it here?
Yes, I do. Which part would you like?
Are you saying you know which part I did?
You know everything, Mr. Yakan.
You must be very fond of orcas. Killer whales.
He loves it.
He probably goes to every site,
It's no exaggeration to say that he watches the members the closest.
Isn't that dangerous?
It's dangerous.
Can I ask you to do the cute part?
I want to see the "kyu-kyu" part. I want to see the kyunky kyunky part.
Dokidoki kyunkyunkyunkyunkyunkyunkyunkyunkyunkyunky.
I'm all for it!
By the way, how about you, Akimoto-san?
Yes.
What did she say?
She was saying that I should get more into it.
It was cute, wasn't it?
How do you think she said it? How do you think Akimoto-san would say it?
Akimoto-san?
She told me to be more crazy about it.
Akimoto-san understands, doesn't he?
He loves her.
You never came back to the dressing room, you were outside all the time.
How did you know?
I'm scared.
Wait.
Kettle, kettle.
Was she in the catering?
He's a hard worker.
I see. I think it was a pod.
That's not true.
Speaking of the usual Sakura-san,
Hmm?
Yes, let me ask you.
Speaking of Sakura san, she always goes back to her dressing room right after the show.
Isn't it your style to go back to your dressing room as soon as the show is over?
That's my motto.It's a motto.
That was the motto. That was.
But he didn't come back to the dressing room and stayed outside during the first and second parts.
I was surprised, Yakan-kun. Were you enjoying yourself?
No, I don't often stay in the hallway like that,
This time, I talked with Yuna Hazuki of Tohoku-san in the hallway,
Yuna is a member of Tohoku who worships Sakura.
She said she wanted a T-shirt and a long T-shirt for her birthday party,
She said she wanted them, so I decided to give them to her at this time and brought them to Osaka.
I gave them to her and told her that she should wash them since they were in a bag.
And I said something like, "Come back! I said something like that,
When Mr. Tohoku's rehearsal started, he covered some of the shirt songs,
It's a color ball.
It's amazing. That's what I expected.
I wonder if it was egosa.
I was egoza.
When I saw him, he was already wearing his birthday T-shirt and playing Powerball,
It was love.
But I was in Sendai and Nagoya, so we didn't have much time to see each other outside of events,
Tohoku-san is also very busy,
So this time I had free time to talk with him.
Speaking of Ms. Wakino, when we all went out on stage after the last 2 minutes of the "Order of the Killer Whale" song, she was sobbing,
You were crying, weren't you?
Yes, that's right.
And you cried too, didn't you, Sakura-san?
I was surprised.
I was surprised to see you crying. You cry.
The last song of the two-minute show was called "Medal of Honor,
It affirms what we have been doing,
Our past activities are our medals,
It is a song that affirms our past activities as our medal, and we are going to move forward with it.
It is a song that really gets us going in the first place,
Before that, Hou-chan expressed her feelings toward the Budokai,
And based on that, we are going to tour all over Japan for the Budokai,
We were all more excited about it because we had such passionate feelings for the Budokai.
So we were really into it.
So, I hope that our fans could understand our passion,
After finishing the medal, Yuna came to the stage crying,
And then Yuna came on stage crying.
The reason why I cried is simply because I saw her,
But I also wondered why Yuna liked me during the talk in the hallway between the shows,
I was also wondering why Yuna had fallen in love with me,
I had been listening to Yuna's geek activities all this time.
What kind of things have you been doing all this time, and at what timing?
I told her that I liked this scene in the Gaikai Hall,
He showed me his YouTube.
I was showing them my own YouTube.
And I was thinking, "I don't remember seeing this part,
I was so happy to know that he was watching me,
I was so happy to see her watching my YouTube,
And then Yuna was crying, and I was happy that she was so supportive of me.
I was so happy that she could feel how I felt.
Yes, it was a good story.
It was a good story.That was a good story.
Yes, it was a pleasure.
It was a nice localism, wasn't it?
Yes, it was.
We have only two months left, so let's make lots of memories.
We will.
Smile will start soon.
Yes, sir.